{
    "subject": "resource/Arthur_Schuster",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arthur_Schuster",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Schuster is primarily about.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8139630556106567,
            "question": "What is Arthur Schuster known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6792751550674438,
            "question": "In what field did Arthur Schuster make significant contributions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6478248834609985,
            "question": "Are there any specific theories or concepts named after Arthur Schuster?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6211634874343872,
            "question": "Who were some of Arthur Schuster's notable contemporaries or collaborators?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5982439517974854,
            "question": "What major scientific discoveries or inventions are associated with Arthur Schuster?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5798113942146301,
            "question": "What were some of the challenges that Arthur Schuster faced in his scientific pursuits?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5442121028900146,
            "question": "Where did Arthur Schuster conduct his research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5231130719184875,
            "question": "How is Arthur Schuster remembered in the history of science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4199419617652893,
            "question": "What impact did Arthur Schuster's work have on subsequent scientific advancements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28398483991622925,
            "question": "What awards or honors did Arthur Schuster receive for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Schuster is primarily about.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4588_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Arthur Schuster's work have on subsequent scientific advancements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4588_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Arthur Schuster remembered in the history of science?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4588_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Arthur Schuster conduct his research?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4588_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4588_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, I will evaluate whether the triple \"Arthur Schuster is primarily about.\" can be supported or not.\n\nHere are my observations:\n\n- There are multiple documents related to Sir/Arthur Schuster, which indicates that he was a notable figure in physics and other fields.\n- The documents mention his work in spectroscopy, electrochemistry, optics, X-radiography, and the application of harmonic analysis to physics. \n- The name \"Schuster's integral\" is mentioned, which further suggests that Arthur Schuster made significant contributions to physics.\n\nConsidering these points, it appears that Arthur Schuster was primarily about physics, making the triple \"yes\". Therefore:\n\nAnswer: {'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sir Arthur Schuster, a British physicist and professor, which supports the statement that the content or primary subject of the documents is about Arthur Schuster."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}